coinmarkets.net 2019-12-18

# Privacy Policy | CoinMarkets

Your privacy is very important to us. At Gecko Labs Pte. Ltd. ("CoinMarkets"), we want to make your experience with us satisfying and safe. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of information we gather from your use of this service (the "Service"), how we use it, with whom we might share it, the means by which we keep it secure, and the choices you have about the information you choose to share with us.

If you have any questions about the privacy practices of CoinMarkets.com or this Privacy Policy, please e-mail info@coinmarkets.net. 

### PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

The types of personal information we collect depend on the product or service you ("You") receive from us. This information may include, but is not limited to:

  * Your name and e-mail address;
  * Your account information, including, but not limited to, account balances and the like;
  * Your demographic information, such as your age, occupation, investment preferences, etc.;
  * Cryptocurrency information (e.g., cryptocurrency ticker symbols), if You create a personalized portfolio, as well as financial information relating to the cryptocurrency You track; and
  * Your usage information

### PERSONAL INFORMATION - WHY WE COLLECT IT

CoinMarkets may collect certain personal information to provide You with the Service, to perform marketing and research related activities, to supply other administrative services (e.g., setting up new accounts and maintaining your existing account), and to respond to inquiries about your account and the Service. In addition we may from time to time review your usage of the Service to be able to better provide you with information about products or services that we believe may be interest to you.

### PERSONAL INFORMATION - HOW WE COLLECT IT

The personal information we collect may be captured from a variety of sources. These sources include, but are not limited to:

  * Voluntary submissions (e.g., responses to surveys, requests for information on our Service, our other products or those of our advertisers/marketing partners);
  * Registrations/Applications to receive the Service; and
  * Reviews of site or app usage patterns

### USE AND ACCESS OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH OTHERS

As a general rule, CoinMarkets will not make the personal information gathered from your using the Service available to anyone outside of CoinMarkets and its affiliates -- except as instructed by You or where required to comply with law, court orders, or legal investigations. Please note, however, that there are several exceptions to this policy. First, if we use service providers, these service providers may have access to your personal information to perform contractually specified services on behalf of CoinMarkets or You. Second, if You indicate that You are interested in receiving information about a particular third party's products/services, or You opt to receive certain products or services through CoinMarkets, we may provide your personal information to that third party for purposes of fulfilling your request(s). With respect to service providers, CoinMarkets contractually requires that all personal information be kept confidential. Additionally, CoinMarkets takes reasonable steps to ensure that third parties receiving information about You at your request maintain the confidentially of that information. 

### LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES

Where applicable, CoinMarkets may provide links to one or more third party Web sites within the Service. We encourage You to read the individual privacy policies of these Websites before providing any of your personal information to them. 

### PROTECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

CoinMarkets puts security measures in place to protect against unauthorized access to, or unauthorized use, alteration, disclosure or destruction of personal information. These measures include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal information.

If You are using a Service on a mobile device, choosing to select "Keep me signed in" will keep your account logged into the Service until You manually log out or change your password. Your User Profile information will still remain password protected. 

CoinMarkets operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided. 

### USE OF COOKIES

CoinMarkets uses Cookies to set user preferences, gather basic tracking information (such as login and password), date, time of visit and preferences, and monitor the presentation of the Service. This information allows us to personalize the user experience and to improve the quality of our Service navigation. Cookies do not reveal the identity of the individual user but only identify the computer utilized by that user. 

Please note that advertisers on the Service may also deploy cookies and other technology to gather users' basic Service usage information (such as pages visited or frequency of visits) for such things as to measure and improve the effectiveness of their advertising. For more information regarding advertisers' practices, including how to opt-out of their cookie tracking, please review the relevant advertisers' privacy policies. 

For more information regarding ad serving network practices, including how to opt-out of their cookie tracking, please visit the ad server's privacy policy at: [http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy.html](https://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy.html)

### ACCURACY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

You are responsible for periodically checking to ensure that your personal information included in Service is updated and correct.

### HOW TO UPDATE PERSONAL INFORMATION

If You desire to update any personal information, You may do so once you've signed in to the Service.

### WHAT ABOUT CHILDREN'S PRI

CoinMarkets does not separately identify, or collect, any information that is specific to children.

### YOUR CONSENT

By using the Service, You consent to the collection and use of your personal information and any related information in the manner and for the purpose described in this Privacy Policy. CoinMarkets's systems are not currently configured to handle 'do not track' requests.

### CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY

CoinMarkets reserves the right to change this policy at any time by distributing and/or posting a new privacy policy without notice. We encourage you to review our privacy policy on a regular basis so that You will be aware of any changes to it.

If you have further questions about our privacy practices, please contact us by e-mailing [info@coinmarkets.net](mailto:info@coinmarkets.net).
